<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>CMARIX</title>
	<atom:link href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://192.168.1.163/blog</link>
	<description>TechnoLabs - Mobile App , Web Application, Website Developement, Hire Expert and Dedicated Resource company</description>
	<lastBuildDate>
	Wed, 16 Sep 2020 13:43:34 +0000	</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.1.5</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Machine Learning for Chatbots: Definition, Processes, and Use Contexts</title>
		<link>http://192.168.1.163/blog/machine-learning-for-chatbots-definition-processes-and-use-contexts/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 13:43:34 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Atman Rathod]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Mobile App Development]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://192.168.1.163/blog/?p=12989</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Chatbots are getting all the buzz and attention in the tech world just because they are awesome to make life easier for customers and businesses with their interactive interfaces. But chatbots are of different types and not all of them are intelligent. While most of them just work as an interactive FAQ interface to answer &#8230; </p>
<p class="link-more"><a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/machine-learning-for-chatbots-definition-processes-and-use-contexts/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Machine Learning for Chatbots: Definition, Processes, and Use Contexts"</span></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/machine-learning-for-chatbots-definition-processes-and-use-contexts/">Machine Learning for Chatbots: Definition, Processes, and Use Contexts</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog">CMARIX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify">Chatbots are getting all the buzz and attention in the tech world just because they are awesome to make life easier for customers and businesses with their interactive interfaces. But chatbots are of different types and not all of them are intelligent. While most of them just work as an interactive FAQ interface to answer predetermined questions, there are intelligent chatbots that learn from user behavior and accordingly recommend products and offer solutions.  Machine learning technology is increasingly being used for this second type of chatbot.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">To understand how machine learning is being used in chatbots development, it is important to understand the different types of chatbots and how machine learning technology can make chatbots communication more intelligent and customer-centric. Here we are going to explain all these attributes that generally any expert <a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/chatbot-development-guide-a-bot-loved-by-travelers/"><b>Chatbot development guide</b></a> would cover.</p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Different Types of Chatbot</b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12993 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/pasted-image-0-8.png" alt="" srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/pasted-image-0-8.png 1121w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/pasted-image-0-8-300x188.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/pasted-image-0-8-768x480.png 768w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/pasted-image-0-8-1024x640.png 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Chatbots are basically interactive automation programs or a conversational tool for automating communication with users. Apart from this core capability, chatbots can be of different types with a variety of features and capabilities. There are chatbots programs that allow the users to interact with a website or a mobile app or a computer program through a chat interface. Chatbots can be used for functional benefits, promotions, guiding customers, solving customer problems, and handling queries and also for entertaining users with interactive conversations.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">The rule-based chatbots used in e-commerce stores mostly serve the purpose of providing customer service. Naturally, they are easier for the developers, involve less technical complexities, and are focused to get the elementary tasks done. But since Artificial Intelligence (AI) and its offset technology Machine Learning have made significant progress in recent times opening new vistas and avenues of machine-led conversation to address customer situations and contexts more accurately, even for the <a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/mobile-application-development-services-india.html"><b>mobile app development services company</b></a> these rule-based chatbots are increasingly getting obsolete and outdated.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><b>Read More:</b> <a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/why-to-build-a-chatbot/">Why to build a ChatBot?</a></p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Machine Learning Chatbots: What Is It?</b><b> </b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12994 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/pasted-image-0-3.png" alt="" srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/pasted-image-0-3.png 1600w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/pasted-image-0-3-300x225.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/pasted-image-0-3-768x576.png 768w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/pasted-image-0-3-1024x768.png 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Machine learning is the subset of AI technology that helps any system learn from the user inputs or user data. In the context of chatbots, the machine learning algorithm will learn from the user inputs and accordingly will give replies and suggest solutions or make recommendations. This learning from the user inputs is taken place through Natural Language Processing (NLP) and a few other technologies within the machine learning ecosystem.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">But intelligent chatbots, besides using machine learning technology, also need to incorporate few other things. The chatbots must ensure that it provides an informative and useful answer to the audience, make the conversation relevant to the context and customer purpose, and above all in tone and choice of words as well as expressions should be felt like human communication. Obviously, even the most capable machine learning chatbots as of now is not capable to replace human gait and expressions.</p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>How To Incorporate Machine Learning Into Chatbots Development?</b><b> </b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Machine Learning now refers to a set of technologies including some established and acclaimed technologies and a few promising new technologies that are still in the making. For example, Natural Language Processing (NLP) is now seen as a constituent machine learning technology for chatbots that help understanding patterns and data-driven insights from large volumes of data. Through the rest of the post, we are going to explain how machine learning and NLP can be incorporated into building chatbots.</p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Data Processing Approaches for Machine Learning Chatbots</b><b> </b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12995 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/chatbot.png" alt="chatbot" srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/chatbot.png 800w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/chatbot-300x225.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/chatbot-768x576.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Clean data that can easily be understood by the chatbots is a crucial requirement for high performance and intelligent chatbots. For effective data processing to make Chatbots work smoothly, several different data processing methods are used now. For preprocessing the data for the chatbot removing stopwords and capital letter and labels are important.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">NLP technology also uses the lexical feature to help to focus on the words instead of sentence structures or grammar. Some preprocessing methods that this lexical approach uses include word-level n-grams, stemming, and lemmatization.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">The syntactic approach to process data uses tagging and chunking the part-of-speech (POS). According to this approach, POS tagging is fine for each word to determine the part of speech for each word including noun, pronoun, verb, etc. The following method is used for partitioning sentences into various segments that are non-overlapping in nature.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">The semantic approach basically helps you to keep your attention fixed on sentence structure while the meaning of words is taken into consideration separately.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Vector Representation is another major approach that uses vector maps to show the high dimensional words to low dimensional words. Every word spoken in the communication comes are subjected to specific rules and relationships to represent the same with vector coordinates. By this approach, closely related words are placed nearby or together. For vector representation, common techniques used by the chatbots include word2vec, doc2vec, and Global Vectors.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><b>Read More:</b> <a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/how-chatbots-instantly-adds-value-to-the-buying-experience-of-todays-consumers/">How Chatbots Instantly Adds Value To The Buying Experience Of Today’s Consumers?</a></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Retrieval technique is widely popular now for understanding short and tiny texts in chatbot conversations. Some machine learning experts and researchers came with this solution to tackle the problem of short length chatbot conversation. As per this approach, a short length and often single-word conversations are collected from different social chat and conversations and are used to train a variety of models.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/inquiry.html?utm_source=CTA_Blogimg"><img class="size-full wp-image-12996 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image-23.png" alt="CTA" srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image-23.png 951w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image-23-300x85.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image-23-768x219.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></a></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">The generation-Based approach is also effective in feeding the chatbot models and it uses basically an encoder-decoder framework. This approach is very similar to the increasingly popular sequence to sequence (seq2seq) model for predicting the next sentence in a conversation.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Long Short-Term Memory (LSTM) network is another major approach that focuses on the probability of creating a response based on previous conversations. This is much similar to the encoder-decoder approach we just explained.</p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Conclusion</b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">In spite of the promises of huge and nearly sci-fi capability that machine learning technology offers for automated conversation, the progress in making self-sustained, fully intelligent chatbots capable of responding to a multitude of scenarios is still slow. But since machine learning chatbots appeared as a revolutionary way forward in the digital landscape, the efforts and research are going to live up to these promises sooner or later. Machine learning chatbots are a reality and they are going to be better and more capable in the years to come.</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/machine-learning-for-chatbots-definition-processes-and-use-contexts/">Machine Learning for Chatbots: Definition, Processes, and Use Contexts</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog">CMARIX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
									<featured_image>http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/machine-learning-in-chatbots-development.png</featured_image>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Is The Importance Of Third Party Code Audit And How To Go About It?</title>
		<link>http://192.168.1.163/blog/what-is-the-importance-of-third-party-code-audit-and-how-to-go-about-it/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 14:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Atman Rathod]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Website Development]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://192.168.1.163/blog/?p=12981</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>These days most software applications reuse codes written by other programmers. This is also the reason why it is important to audit the code to make sure that by reusing the code no security vulnerability is incorporated into the development. At any point in time when a software code is used by different hands, it &#8230; </p>
<p class="link-more"><a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/what-is-the-importance-of-third-party-code-audit-and-how-to-go-about-it/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "What Is The Importance Of Third Party Code Audit And How To Go About It?"</span></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/what-is-the-importance-of-third-party-code-audit-and-how-to-go-about-it/">What Is The Importance Of Third Party Code Audit And How To Go About It?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog">CMARIX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify">These days most software applications reuse codes written by other programmers. This is also the reason why it is important to audit the code to make sure that by reusing the code no security vulnerability is incorporated into the development. At any point in time when a software code is used by different hands, it is important to understand the underlying composition, pedigree, ownership, and licensing as well as obligations.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">The code audit which is different from the software audit is done to detect the ready to use code you have used in your development including the software modules, packages, files, or just a few lines of external code. The auditing process apart from ensuring code ownership and licensing obligations can also point out the issues with the application code. Whether you are a software or a <a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/"><b>Web App Development Company</b></a><b>, </b>you must be needing code review from time to time.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Here we are going to explain some of the key reasons to conduct code audits.</p>

<ul>
 	<li><b>Enhanced Programming Quality
</b></li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12983 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Screenshot-23.png" alt="" srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Screenshot-23.png 712w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Screenshot-23-300x219.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 712px) 100vw, 712px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">We all know the important role of QA testing in enhancing the performance of an app product. Similarly, source code reviews are equally important to ensure higher code quality. With the review of the source code, developers can easily improve software performance and can expand the software product by adding new features.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Enhanced code quality also makes sure that the developers need to spend the least time and resources in solving technical issues and errors. The code debt which is common for development companies using code created by other developers should be reviewed and technically perfected.</p>

<ul>
 	<li><b>Cost Advantage
</b></li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify">To reduce the cost of development it is important to detect the bugs early and as quickly as possible. Thanks to code audit detecting and resolving errors at the initial stage of development ensure a great cost advantage for the software projects. The external developers can easily detect mistakes made by external software developers.</p>

<ul>
 	<li><b>Streamlined Development Process
</b></li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12984 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Development-Process.png" alt="Development Process" srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Development-Process.png 1600w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Development-Process-300x225.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Development-Process-768x576.png 768w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Development-Process-1024x768.png 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Undetected coding mistakes lying within can cause further development issues down the line and can undermine the project management. Apart from detecting and addressing bugs and errors for enhancing software quality, the code audit also improves and streamlines the software development processes and the developer team output.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><b>Learn</b>: <a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/key-security-practices-that-most-leading-ecommerce-audit-specialists-prescribe/">Key Security Practices That Most Leading eCommerce Audit Specialists Prescribe</a></p>

<ul>
 	<li><b>Improving the Skills of New Developers
</b></li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify">The code audit also helps new and less experienced developers get familiar and improve skills with different modules and other development practices. Thanks to the code audit and review it becomes easier for the development teams to share ideas and improve development skills. The younger and less experienced developers through code review and audit can easily sharpen their development skills and develop expertise for the coding tasks.</p>

<ul>
 	<li><b>Making More Precise and Accurate Project Estimation
</b></li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12985 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Accurate-Project-Estimation.jpg" alt="Accurate Project Estimation " srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Accurate-Project-Estimation.jpg 750w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Accurate-Project-Estimation-300x160.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 706px) 89vw, (max-width: 767px) 82vw, 740px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Code audit also facilitates sharing coding skills and knowledge among developers and helps to pass the expertise from the original author to other developers. As the reviewer of the code is likely to be familiar and versed with the different issues common in the code base he can make recommendations about changes as per the complexity of the project. This allows making more precise and accurate estimates of the software development project in terms of cost, development time, and required resources.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/inquiry.html?utm_source=CTA_Blogimg"><img class="size-full wp-image-12986 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image98.png" alt="CTA" srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image98.png 951w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image98-300x85.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image98-768x219.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></a></p>

<ul>
 	<li><b>Maintaining Consistency in Coding Style
</b></li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify">Code audit also ensures maintaining consistency of coding style all through a software development project. Thanks to the code audit any developer joining in the middle of a project can easily understand the code and get engaged quickly with the tasks. With the easy to read source code of a software, the developers can also reduce the development cost and spending of resources in the long run.</p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>How to Go About Software Code Audit? </b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12987 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/About-Software-Code-Audit.jpg" alt="About Software Code Audit" srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/About-Software-Code-Audit.jpg 1600w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/About-Software-Code-Audit-300x225.jpg 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/About-Software-Code-Audit-768x576.jpg 768w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/About-Software-Code-Audit-1024x768.jpg 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">You need to set up an automatic code scanning process once after meeting the legal requirements the software code is made available for the project. First, you need to identify and segregate the constituent modules and then carry out scanning the code.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Through the scanning of the code, you can get warnings about ownership obligations, copyright information, licensing requirements, etc. now these reports containing the details about the used software will be reviewed by the auditing team. Depending upon the project complexities, this scanning process can take up to 2 days.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Let us now have a quick look at the different steps of carrying out code audits.</p>

<ul>
 	<li>When the code audit is carried out manually, it goes through three different phases, respectively as reviewing of frontend code, backend code, and infrastructure.</li>
 	<li>The reviewing of the front end code takes care of detecting coding issues impacting the user experience like the loading speed.</li>
 	<li>The review of the backend code goes deeper into the core codebase for finding how the code is interacting with and accommodating other tools. This review process also analyses the security vulnerabilities.</li>
 	<li>The infrastructure review finally takes holistic care of a lot of aspects of a system including the hardware, software application, development processes, and the responsibilities. This review process is also about enforcing best development practices and following widely acclaimed system recommendations.</li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify">Now that we have explained the processes of code auditing, we need to spare a few words on the challenges and precautions regarding code audit. A code auditing process can be a really challenging task with the responsibility of reviewing thousands of code lines. This is why it is ideal to make use of a checklist and break down the entire review process into different modules to concentrate on reviewing each module separately.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Generally, software engineers from both the team of the original software producer and the buyer company review the code and they become familiar with the software functionalities and the structure of the software. Now, a deeper manual audit is carried out for the frontend, backend, and infrastructure of the software. At last, all the auditing reports are compiled into a comprehensive report listing various issues and corresponding solutions.</p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Conclusion</b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">As long as software development will encourage collaboration and reusability of other’s coding, code audit will remain essential. Since the development world is increasingly becoming collaborative and interdependent, code audit is likely to remain a mainstay for the years to come.</p>
&nbsp;<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/what-is-the-importance-of-third-party-code-audit-and-how-to-go-about-it/">What Is The Importance Of Third Party Code Audit And How To Go About It?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog">CMARIX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
									<featured_image>http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Why-is-third-party-code-audit-is-important-for-your-custom-software.png</featured_image>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Most Effective Blockchain Design Principles For Organizations and Businesses</title>
		<link>http://192.168.1.163/blog/most-effective-blockchain-design-principles-for-organizations-and-businesses/</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 13:41:34 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Atman Rathod]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[FrontEnd Development]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://192.168.1.163/blog/?p=12970</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>While Blockchain technology is new to most users across the spectrum, it is important to design Blockchain-powered databases and solutions simple enough for encouraging usability and traction. This is why Blockchain design principles appear to be so important in the present state of things. Whether it is the UX designing and prototyping for startups or &#8230; </p>
<p class="link-more"><a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/most-effective-blockchain-design-principles-for-organizations-and-businesses/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Most Effective Blockchain Design Principles For Organizations and Businesses"</span></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/most-effective-blockchain-design-principles-for-organizations-and-businesses/">Most Effective Blockchain Design Principles For Organizations and Businesses</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog">CMARIX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify">While Blockchain technology is new to most users across the spectrum, it is important to design Blockchain-powered databases and solutions simple enough for encouraging usability and traction. This is why Blockchain design principles appear to be so important in the present state of things. Whether it is the <a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/design-prototyping-services.html"><b>UX designing and prototyping for startups</b></a> or designing a mobile Fintech app powered by Blockchain, design considerations should be at the center stage.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Here we are going to explain some of the key Blockchain design principles.</p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Reconciling With User Expectations</b><b> </b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">There are users who need more exposure to the data in blockchain databases compared to the others. There will still be users who need to track how the blockchain is actually replacing earlier processes only to gain confidence and trust.  It is also important for all users to understand how Blockchain works to allow more security for their data.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">To make things easier the Blockchain experts should always control exposure to data with cryptographic mechanisms. The traditional Blockchain practices like using those long cryptographic hashes are still effective in spite of the fact that they are least readable by humans. Users generally finding these complex codes develop trust in Blockchain security power.</p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Maintaining Visual Consistency</b><b> </b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12973 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/pasted-image-0-7.png" alt="" srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/pasted-image-0-7.png 800w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/pasted-image-0-7-300x225.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/pasted-image-0-7-768x576.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">One of the key aspects leading to the trustworthiness of a software product is maintaining visual consistency. The design layout apart from ensuring consistency throughout the interface should also be easy to use, relevant to the user activities and purposes, and highly proportional. Using a grid layout along with clean typefaces and a lot of negative space can be very effective.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Do you want to give simple visual clues to Blockchain actions that make the interface more intuitive? Well, there cannot be a better way to engage users than using simple and consistently placed icons for different actions. But while using visual metaphors make sure they remain thoroughly understandable with an obvious link to conventional meaning.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><b>Read More: </b><a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/blockchain-technology-in-healthcare-the-growth-story-statistics-and-promises/">Blockchain Technology In Healthcare: The Growth Story, Statistics And Promises</a></p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Continuous Feedback</b><b> </b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12974 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/bootstrapdash.png" alt="bootstrapdash" srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/bootstrapdash.png 800w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/bootstrapdash-300x225.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/bootstrapdash-768x576.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">By accommodating continuous feedback developers should ensure user understanding of whatever taking place beyond their eyes and thereby reduce their concerns. It is important to utilize both motion and animation to provide feedback on every in-app action.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Accommodating feedback elements and micro-interactions is extremely important to gain the user&#8217;s confidence and get an idea of what is underway and what is going to happen. Since Blockchain applications involve multiple processes, providing appropriate visual feedback is extremely important. When you are putting your valuable efforts to improve <a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/how-the-evolution-of-mobile-security-better-with-blockchain/"><b>mobile security with blockchain</b></a>, creating the right feedback interactions is of extreme significance.</p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Design Communication Should Be Given a Priority</b><b> </b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12975 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Design-Communication.png" alt="Design Communication" srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Design-Communication.png 1600w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Design-Communication-300x225.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Design-Communication-768x576.png 768w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Design-Communication-1024x768.png 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Communication through the design should be given a priority in the scheme of things. A Blockchain app will be addressed to a variety of users across diverse ethnicities and languages. Since feature-rich Blockchain apps taking care of all-round data security are popular, you cannot pull down their usability by taking importance to user communication.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Some of the most helpful principles to improve communication of your Blockchain app include the following.</p>

<ul>
 	<li>First of all, make sure you have global temperament while designing the app as it is likely to be used by apps of different language groups and cultural backgrounds.</li>
 	<li>Make sure you continuously take user feedback and accordingly take steps to improve the software product.</li>
 	<li>Make sure you come with frequent design enhancements to help users complete tasks more swiftly.</li>
 	<li>Try to engage with the user community holding discussions about ways to improve the design aspects.</li>
</ul>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Rectify Issues and Errors Quickly</b><b> </b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12976 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Errors-Quickly.png" alt="Errors Quickly" srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Errors-Quickly.png 1600w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Errors-Quickly-300x225.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Errors-Quickly-768x576.png 768w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Errors-Quickly-1024x768.png 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">While trying to enhance the Blockchain app design, what you should always remember is that fine-tuning the product based on user response and feedback should be a consistent and continuous process, and addressing issues and errors should not be delayed. Since Blockchain technology is crucial to data security, any erroneous aspect can harm the trustworthiness of the solution.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Since errors and issues cannot be avoided completely, it is important to stay vigilant on these errors and faultlines that keep coming every once in a while. Apart from trying to solve most of the errors and issues in the design and development stage, make sure you can come with solutions to get rid of errors once the Blockchain app is in active use.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/inquiry.html?utm_source=CTA_Blogimg"><img class="size-full wp-image-12977 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image-22.png" alt="CTA" srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image-22.png 951w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image-22-300x85.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image-22-768x219.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></a></p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Uncompromising Sustainability</b><b> </b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Now let us point out one of the most important aspects of Blockchain development. Since Blockchain is already as popular as the most credible and advanced database technology with zero data breaching and tampering risks, blockchain-based apps are on the rise. This is why it is important to make sure that the ground principles corresponding to systems such as using trust models ensuring optimum data visibility and competitive cost advantage are maintained throughout an app. By following these principles, a Blockchain app can be more sustainable.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">There is also a contradiction related to the sustainability of the Blockchain app. While a sustainable Blockchain app with the most reliable practices and features allow smooth collaboration within an open environment, it also ensures that certain systems like trust models and governance systems like smart contracts remain locked. Maintaining the sustainability of Blockchain apps basically means creating a balance between these two opposites.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><b>Read More:</b><a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/the-impactful-role-of-blockchain-on-wordpress-plugin-development/"> The Impactful Role Of Blockchain On WordPress Plugin Development</a></p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Conclusion</b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">There are huge interest and excitement over the use of blockchain technology for more efficient data usage, analytical and data storage powered by smooth access. Since solving data security issues has been a key objective of too many enterprises and organizations over the years, the emergence of Blockchain has been received with such thumping appreciation. In just a couple of years, Blockchain became the most talked-of technology for enterprise data security. But unlocking the power of Blockchain is not easy if you do not make a balance between the established convention and innovative design.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">With these design considerations addressed adequately and appropriately, many of the Blockchain applications can emerge as truly powerful and effective to address data concerns of all types across enterprises and organizations.</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/most-effective-blockchain-design-principles-for-organizations-and-businesses/">Most Effective Blockchain Design Principles For Organizations and Businesses</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog">CMARIX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
									<featured_image>http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Blockchain-Design-principles.png</featured_image>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Step By Step Guide To Develop A Successful Fleet Management Business</title>
		<link>http://192.168.1.163/blog/the-quick-guide-to-start-a-fleet-management-company-online/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 13:49:20 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Atman Rathod]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Android App Development]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://192.168.1.163/blog/?p=12959</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Your assessment is quite right if you find the fleet management business lucrative now. Yes, after the global pandemic of Covid-19 gave a huge positive push to the demands of doorstep delivery of commodities, efficiency became more important for the entire logistics and goods transport industry. Hi-tech means including telematics and fleet management solutions are &#8230; </p>
<p class="link-more"><a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/the-quick-guide-to-start-a-fleet-management-company-online/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "A Step By Step Guide To Develop A Successful Fleet Management Business"</span></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/the-quick-guide-to-start-a-fleet-management-company-online/">A Step By Step Guide To Develop A Successful Fleet Management Business</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog">CMARIX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify"><span style="font-weight: 400">Your assessment is quite right if you find the fleet management business lucrative now. Yes, after the global pandemic of Covid-19 gave a huge positive push to the demands of doorstep delivery of commodities, efficiency became more important for the entire logistics and goods transport industry. Hi-tech means including telematics and fleet management solutions are increasingly paving the way for enhanced efficiency. So, if you want to enter the fleet management business, there cannot be a better time than now. </span></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><span style="font-weight: 400">The market of fleet management solutions is expected to grow from $13.78 billion to $28.66 billion starting from 2017 to 2022. As the more efficient and tech-driven logistics solutions are increasingly becoming the key aspect of the industries around the world, fleet management solutions are future-proof enough to accommodate evolving business needs and increasing demands of the global supply chain. </span></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><span style="font-weight: 400">But building a fleet management business powered by a hi-tech solution is not easy if you are not versed with the intricacies of the business and various challenges. Here we explain all the steps for building a successful fleet management business.</span></p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Fix Your Goals </b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12961 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Fix-Your-Goals.jpg" alt="Fix Your Goals " srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Fix-Your-Goals.jpg 626w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Fix-Your-Goals-300x199.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 626px) 100vw, 626px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><span style="font-weight: 400">While the fleet management solutions in the market are way too many, each one of them is different and offers specific sets of solutions to fulfill specific business needs. This is why you need to have a clear idea about your business goal and a detailed business plan explaining things you want to do and the way you want to do them. </span></p>
<span style="font-weight: 400">For making a comprehensive business plan ask the following questions. </span>
<ul>
 	<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Who will be the primary target audience of your solution and how it will benefit the audience?</span></li>
 	<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">What are the key ways you will handle the expenses of managing the fleet? Are you going to buy the tricks or take them on lease? </span></li>
 	<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">What kind of marketing plan do you have in place? How do you market your solution on digital platforms? </span></li>
 	<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Where are you going to hire the workforce? Are you going to hire directly or going to hire people contractually through a third-party workforce management company? </span></li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify"><span style="font-weight: 400">By replying to these questions with specific answers you can have a comprehensive and complete business plan ready. Once you have the business plan ready, you can try to rope in investors. </span></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/inquiry.html?utm_source=CTA_Blogimg"><img class="size-full wp-image-12962 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image9.png" alt="CTA Blog Inquiry" srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image9.png 951w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image9-300x85.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image9-768x219.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></a></p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Meeting Compliance and Regulatory Obligations </b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><span style="font-weight: 400">The next important step is to meet the compliance standards and regulatory obligations to operate as a fleet management company in the international business. Some of these regulations pertain to the government ruling and norms and some regulations are industry-specific. You need to have strong command over all the rules, regulations, and norms that are existing in the sector. From generating special licenses and numbers for cross-state and cross-country fleet operations to meeting fuel regulations for your vehicles, you need to stay tuned to every norm. </span></p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Finding the Perfect Software for Fleet Management </b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12963 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/shot.png" alt="inding the Perfect Software for Fleet Management " srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/shot.png 800w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/shot-300x225.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/shot-768x576.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><span style="font-weight: 400">Apart from dealing with all the administrative hassles and critical business dynamics including strategies and planning, you also need great software for fleet management.  There is no question of managing your fleets of vehicles manually and without any software help, since the software in the entire sector ensures delivering optimum efficiency and productivity besides handling the load of most common tasks. </span></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><span style="font-weight: 400">But when it comes to picking a dedicated fleet management software you have several great choices at your disposal. Most of the leading software solutions presently in use across fleet management companies take care of tracking the on-road vehicles and the driver activities, need for vehicle maintenance, and many other days to day tasks. Obviously, these software programs make the job of the managers and the business owners easier by streamlining various tasks without manual help. You can also hire a </span><a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/software-product-development.html"><b>digital product development company</b></a> <span style="font-weight: 400">with experience in this sector for building custom software for your business. </span></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><span style="font-weight: 400">When choosing a great fleet management software look for the most important features such as mobile access, tracking driver movements, and behaviour, tracking fuel level and fuel efficiency, vehicle maintenance, an electronic inspection of the vehicles, panic alerts, and several others. The software must take loads of daily repetitive tasks off the shoulders of the management and ensure a streamlined process. You should also ensure to have a preventive maintenance alert feature to take care of the vehicles in time. </span></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><span style="font-weight: 400"><strong>Learn</strong>: </span><a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/mobile-telematics-the-smart-way-for-brands-to-unlock-power-of-vehicles/"><span style="font-weight: 400">Mobile Telematics: The Smart Way For Brands To Unlock Power Of Vehicles</span></a></p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Hiring the Workforce </b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><span style="font-weight: 400">After you have a dedicated fleet management software in place and you can assess the tasks that are going to be automated, it is time to hire the drivers and fleet management staff for running the company. You can either choose to hire all dedicated drivers all on your own or just can engage a third-party workforce provider company to deal with the hiring tasks who will employ the drivers on a contract basis. </span></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><span style="font-weight: 400">While the first approach comes with a lot of cost overhead and is regarded to be expensive, it allows better integration of the workforce with the company and better quality output. The second approach can be less expensive involving less overhead cost over time, but you need to risk hiring non-efficient drivers and personnel through this process. </span></p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Automate the Operation and Cut Costs  </b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12964 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Automate-the-Operation-and-Cut-Costs.png" alt="Automate the Operation and Cut Costs " srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Automate-the-Operation-and-Cut-Costs.png 1599w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Automate-the-Operation-and-Cut-Costs-300x225.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Automate-the-Operation-and-Cut-Costs-768x576.png 768w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Automate-the-Operation-and-Cut-Costs-1024x768.png 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><span style="font-weight: 400">Now you need to take some proactive and effective measures to cut the operational cost which is crucial to stay competitive and growing as a business. The best way to control operational costs is to use great operation software that takes care of the entire fleet management tasks. If you have chosen a dedicated fleet management software it may already have several features to automate operational tasks. Otherwise, you need to choose one operation software that just fits in your business and helps to automate most day to day business operation tasks. </span></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><span style="font-weight: 400">An operational software solution can take care of all the aspects starting from making the right bids for the parcels to managing the driver schedules to taking care of their salaries and tracking fuel purchases, all day to day tasks can be automated and completed in a streamlined manner by using the operational software solutions. </span></p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Ensure Having the Required Financial Strength </b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><span style="font-weight: 400">Now you have a fair idea of all the areas needing investments and so you need to make sure you have the right financial resources at your disposal. Since as a business you need to stay on the market for some time before actually contracts to flow in opening new revenue opportunities, you need to have the arrangement of a strong fund corpus to take care of all the salaries, vehicle maintenance, on-road costs, and fuel costs. Remember, financial strength is a crucial component for any fleet management business and you cannot compromise on that. </span></p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Have Business Analytics in Place </b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12965 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Have-Business-Analytics-in-Place.png" alt="Have Business Analytics in Place " srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Have-Business-Analytics-in-Place.png 1600w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Have-Business-Analytics-in-Place-300x225.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Have-Business-Analytics-in-Place-768x576.png 768w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Have-Business-Analytics-in-Place-1024x768.png 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><span style="font-weight: 400">To mention at the last but not the least emphasis, every successful business especially the ones operating in a highly competitive and demanding sector like fleet management needs the power of analytics to keep track of anything that goes wrong and all the aspects that can be optimised for an improved business outcome. You need to carry out internal and external audits from time to time to ensure everything goes in the right direction. Choose a great business analytics software that keeps you sending alerts on anything that requires immediate attention.  </span></p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Conclusion</b><span style="font-weight: 400"> </span></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><span style="font-weight: 400">Running a fleet management business is not easy. But the presence of sophisticated fleet management software solutions makes things easier for new businesses in this sector. Automating maximum tasks with a strong eye on areas that are flagged as weak or under-optimized while keeping the financial strength and morale high, this is the right chemistry that makes a successful fleet management brand. </span></p>
&nbsp;<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/the-quick-guide-to-start-a-fleet-management-company-online/">A Step By Step Guide To Develop A Successful Fleet Management Business</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog">CMARIX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
									<featured_image>http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/How-to-Start-a-Profitable-Fleet-Management-Business.png</featured_image>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>All New WordPress 5.5: The Key Value Additions For The Web Developers</title>
		<link>http://192.168.1.163/blog/all-new-wordpress-5-5-the-key-value-additions-for-the-web-developers/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 14:12:09 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Atman Rathod]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Wordpress Development]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://192.168.1.163/blog/?p=12949</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Do we still need to elaborate on the popularity of the WordPress platform which is behind 37% of websites presently running all over the globe? WordPress is being embraced by hundreds of new websites each day. This humongous popularity of the platform can mainly be attributed to the frequent updates and streamlined maintenance that WordPress &#8230; </p>
<p class="link-more"><a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/all-new-wordpress-5-5-the-key-value-additions-for-the-web-developers/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "All New WordPress 5.5: The Key Value Additions For The Web Developers"</span></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/all-new-wordpress-5-5-the-key-value-additions-for-the-web-developers/">All New WordPress 5.5: The Key Value Additions For The Web Developers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog">CMARIX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify">Do we still need to elaborate on the popularity of the WordPress platform which is behind 37% of websites presently running all over the globe? WordPress is being embraced by hundreds of new websites each day. This humongous popularity of the platform can mainly be attributed to the frequent updates and streamlined maintenance that WordPress is subjected to.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Very recently we have the WordPress 5.5 update with a lot of new value additions that WordPress users will be delighted with. The update has hit the market by integrating several features for which users needed to rely on third-party apps previously. Here we are going to explain the key features of this new WordPress update apart from sparing some words on the rolling of WordPress 5.5.</p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>The Rolling of WordPress 5.5 </b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12953 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/WordPress-5.5.png" alt="WordPress 5.5" srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/WordPress-5.5.png 1600w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/WordPress-5.5-300x169.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/WordPress-5.5-768x432.png 768w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/WordPress-5.5-1024x576.png 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">The WordPress 5.5 has already been unleashed in the market with a beta version loaded with several inbuilt features and plugins that you can readily use in your WordPress website. The beta versions already claimed to have perfected dozens of bugs and came with several improvements. As the final version is already out, we can expect it to offer a conclusive and comprehensive approach to improving the WordPress web experience.</p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Most Notable Features of WordPress 5.5</b><b> </b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12954 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Worpress-5.png" alt="Worpress-5" srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Worpress-5.png 800w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Worpress-5-300x225.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Worpress-5-768x576.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">As we have already explained, the WordPress 5.5 version is loaded with several new features and value additions ranging from a new block editor to inbuilt lazy loading of graphics. Expectedly, these value additions and features are likely to help any <a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wordpress-web-development-services.html"><b>custom WordPress development company</b></a> in respect of making their websites better.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><b>-&gt; Inbuilt Lazy Loading Feature of WordPress 5.5</b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">WordPress 5.5 has come with enhancements to help web browsers to lazy load graphic contents and images. Thanks to such inbuilt features, the users and the webmasters can experience significant performance improvements while also saving the bandwidth for the users, hosts, and ISPs. When accessing the web content on a slow connection, the images can load in the background while the users still can access the content they need.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><b>-&gt; Integrated Website Sitemaps</b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12955 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Website-Sitemaps.png" alt="Website Sitemaps" srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Website-Sitemaps.png 800w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Website-Sitemaps-300x225.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Website-Sitemaps-768x576.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">A website sitemap helps the search engines to identify and locate the relevant content as per the search terms. Earlier WordPress websites have to use third-party plugins for sitemaps. Now the WordPress 5.5 comes with an integrated XML sitemap feature to ensure optimum visibility and easy search engine finding of your pages and contents.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/inquiry.html?utm_source=CTA_Blogimg"><img class="size-full wp-image-12956 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image-21.png" alt="CTA" srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image-21.png 951w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image-21-300x85.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image-21-768x219.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></a></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><b>-&gt; Enhanced Accessibility
</b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Another great value addition that WordPress 5.5 comes equipped with its enhanced accessibility features. This is something that the core WordPress development team before coming with any version update of the content management system comes to introduce. Improved accessibility is also improving the convenience of using the platform.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Let us have a quick look at the key improvements that WordPress 5.5 offered in regard to accessibility.</p>

<ul>
 	<li>The tables lists offer now more options and alternative views</li>
 	<li>The listed links can now be converted into HTML 5 based navigation blocks.</li>
 	<li>Just with a single tap on the button, the site admin can make a copy of the links shown on the modal dialogues and media screen.</li>
 	<li>The disabled buttons will appear now as disabled</li>
 	<li>The website admin can now use keyboards to move the meta boxes.</li>
 	<li>The front page website logo will not be linked to the front page</li>
 	<li>Through the image editor status, messages can be shown to the assistive devices.</li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify"><b>-&gt; Enhanced Block Editor
</b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12957 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Block-Editor.png" alt="Block Editor" srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Block-Editor.png 800w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Block-Editor-300x225.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Block-Editor-768x576.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">One of the biggest and most notable value additions of the WordPress 5.5 is the new and improved block editor. There is big speculation that the new version has made as many as 500 enhancements to provide an unmatched block editor experience. Some of the key-value additions and features of the new block editor include the following.</p>

<ul>
 	<li>Inline image editing of the new block editor will allow WordPress users to crop, rotate, and zoom images directly while using the block editor. This will be really time-saving and is expected to keep the errors at a minimum.</li>
 	<li>The new block editor will also offer a lot of prebuilt block patterns to help to develop multilayered pages without much pain and effort. This will also allow users to come up with their own unique blocks for their websites. Block patterns are prebuilt templates that users can incorporate into their website pages.</li>
 	<li>The UI of the block editor has also been improved by adding icons, borders around the toolbars, new icons, focus lighting, etc.</li>
 	<li>The new block editor also allows integrating third-party block patterns without any compatibility issues.</li>
 	<li>Seamless and smooth editing experience requiring least effort.</li>
 	<li>The new block editor will also provide articulate device previews to see how the content will look at different device screens.</li>
 	<li>The new block editor will offer great editing experience with features like moving blocks, drag and drop, parent block section, multi-select formatting, etc.</li>
 	<li>You can easily add backgrounds and gradients to blocks.</li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify"><b>-&gt; Auto-Updating of Themes and Plugins
</b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">As of now one of the common advice that most WordPress users had to listen to is updating the plugins and themes regularly to avail the latest security patches and other improvements. Fortunately, WordPress 5.5 made your job easier as from now WordPress will auto-update the plugins and themes periodically.</p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Conclusion</b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">WordPress 5.5 update has been one of the most significant releases considering the wide spectrum of features and value additions it helps s offering to the users. Make sure you have already upgraded to WordPress 5.5.</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/all-new-wordpress-5-5-the-key-value-additions-for-the-web-developers/">All New WordPress 5.5: The Key Value Additions For The Web Developers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog">CMARIX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
									<featured_image>http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Reach-a-new-milestone-with-the-new-WordPress-5.png</featured_image>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Artificial Intelligence Is Transforming Healthcare IT Systems?</title>
		<link>http://192.168.1.163/blog/how-artificial-intelligence-is-transforming-healthcare-it-systems/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 13:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Atman Rathod]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://192.168.1.163/blog/?p=12941</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Lime in many other fields artificial intelligence (AI) is continuing to transform the healthcare industry and medical treatment. AI as we already know makes the promise of creating intelligent automation for many business processes ensuring optimum productivity and efficiency. In the context of healthcare along with these aspects, AI is also playing a key role &#8230; </p>
<p class="link-more"><a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/how-artificial-intelligence-is-transforming-healthcare-it-systems/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "How Artificial Intelligence Is Transforming Healthcare IT Systems?"</span></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/how-artificial-intelligence-is-transforming-healthcare-it-systems/">How Artificial Intelligence Is Transforming Healthcare IT Systems?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog">CMARIX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify">Lime in many other fields artificial intelligence (AI) is continuing to transform the healthcare industry and medical treatment. AI as we already know makes the promise of creating intelligent automation for many business processes ensuring optimum productivity and efficiency. In the context of healthcare along with these aspects, AI is also playing a key role in saving the lives of people and improving their health.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">With so much promise unfolded by the AI in healthcare, it is important to take a closer look at the various facets and areas of healthcare and pharma where the AI is showing the biggest promises. From medical professionals to patients to any leading <a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/healthcare-platform-development.html"><b>Healthcare Software Development Company</b></a>, the promise of AI is looming large to every stakeholder in the sector. Here we are going to explain these areas one by one.</p>

<ul>
 	<li><b>Virtual Assistants</b></li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify">AI-based virtual assistants that are already being used across websites, gadgets, and mobile apps have also made their presence felt in the healthcare sector. For certain patients who have difficulties in moving around for their daily needs and carrying out daily activities, intelligent virtual assistants have emerged the most useful help. People suffering from Alzheimer’s disease can easily find help from intelligent virtual assistants coming with mobile and smart speaker platforms. For example, Alexa virtual assistants coming with Amazon Echo can help a patient with reminders about taking bath, medicines, or food.</p>

<ul>
 	<li><b>Robotic Treatment
</b></li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12943 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Robotic-Treatment.png" alt="Robotic Treatment " srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Robotic-Treatment.png 726w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Robotic-Treatment-300x190.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 726px) 100vw, 726px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Helping patients in diverse medical situations with intelligent robots have emerged as a new trend. For example, some clinics are already using AI-powered robots in helping patients to recover after suffering a stroke. A robotic arm by using digital algorithms can detect the motions that patients are incapable of and accordingly helps patients to make those motions.</p>

<ul>
 	<li><b>AI Guided Medical Diagnosis</b></li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify">AI is playing an instrumental role in improving the accuracy and precision of the medical diagnosis. Already FDA has approved such intelligent software that allows healthcare professionals to take ECG images of the heart of patients without having any specialised training for the same. Machine Learning technology which is a subset of AI is also being utilised to capture the high-quality ultrasound images of the heart and record the video clips.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Artificial Intelligence (AI) in multiple ways is helping the medical fraternity in diagnosing diseases based on patient symptoms and detecting anomalies. Many cancer cases are diagnosed at the advanced stages as the symptoms often remain undetected or are confused with other regular diseases. This is where AI can make a great help. An AI-powered platform is already being developed that can help to identify and detect the signs of cancer at the early stages.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><b>Learn:</b> <a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/key-principles-and-trends-for-building-a-user-focused-healthcare-website/">Key Principles and Trends for Building a User-Focused Healthcare Website</a></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">AI-based radiology and imaging techniques are now coming with a deeper interpretation of the medical images. For many cancer cases, AI is actively helping to reduce false-positive cases by using deep learning techniques and intelligent interpretation. It has already been established that for detecting skin cancers AI-based diagnostic solutions work great in coming with more precise results.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Another area in the area of medical diagnosis that is going to be hugely transformed is the mobile app-based diagnosis of medical conditions with the help of AI. For example, AI will allow mobile apps to scan the eyes and detect certain symptoms and the specially-abled touch interface will be able to gather data about the pulse rate and blood pressure rates that further can be analysed by an AI-powered diagnostic app.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/inquiry.html?utm_source=CTA_Blogimg"><img class="size-full wp-image-12944 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image89.png" alt="CTA" srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image89.png 951w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image89-300x85.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image89-768x219.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></a></p>

<ul>
 	<li><b>New Drug Discovery and Development
</b></li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12945 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Discovery-and-Development.png" alt="Discovery and Development " srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Discovery-and-Development.png 800w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Discovery-and-Development-300x223.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Discovery-and-Development-768x571.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Multiple pharma brands and medical laboratories and research institutions are now using Artificial Intelligence to find new drugs and are achieving success in lowering the time and resources required for the new drug discovery and development processes. After the <a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/telemedicine-apps-the-next-big-digital-revolution-of-healthcare-is-the-offing/"><b>telemedicine apps</b></a> swept the pharma sector in many countries, they are putting their next bet on AI-based drug discovery. In the age of artificial intelligence, pharma companies are trying to live up to the promise of faster drug discovery and quicker time to market for the drugs.</p>

<ul>
 	<li><b>Efficient Clinical Trials</b></li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify">In most parts of the world, clinical trials for newly discovered drugs go through a very under-managed process with no integrated mechanism to keep track of the entire process and evaluation of the trial results more accurately. This is where AI has offered big promise in enhancing the capability to analyse results, finding anomalies, and detecting symptoms and side effects at different stages of the trials. Thanks to AI, clinical trials can now be carried out in a more professional and well organised manner besides improving the precision and accuracy of trial outcomes.</p>

<ul>
 	<li><b>Comforting Patients
</b></li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12946 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Comforting-Patients.gif" alt="Comforting Patients" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Some painful diseases and health conditions require distracting patient’s attention to something engaging and immersive. This is where the AI-driven simulated virtual reality can play a big role. The VR programs with intelligent simulations running on a bedside screen or on the screen of headgear can keep patients engaged and thus can distract his or her attention from the pain so that caregivers and the patient&#8217;s family members can be at ease.</p>

<ul>
 	<li><b>AI-Driven Counselling
</b></li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify">Psychological trauma and depression are common causes and outcomes that healthcare experts need to face in many patients in different contexts and situations. This is one area where AI-driven apps and solutions can play a great role in detecting certain behavioural attributes and patient tendencies. AI can help caregivers and healthcare staff find certain signs and symptoms triggering psychological problems in patients and can suggest appropriate behavioural therapies to help patients recover from such conditions.</p>

<ul>
 	<li><b>Personalised Healthcare
</b></li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12947 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Healthcare.jpg" alt="Healthcare" srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Healthcare.jpg 800w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Healthcare-300x225.jpg 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Healthcare-768x576.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Like many other fields, personalisation thanks to the very nature of digital interfaces and technologies that have penetrated deep in the healthcare arena. Personalised healthcare and treatment is one of the key value propositions for modern healthcare facilities around the world. Personalised healthcare services are not just limited to individual communication to patients and caregiving processes, they are also going to change the way drugs are administered and treatment is planned for both chronic and life-threatening diseases.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">With more rigorous data collection mechanisms working across healthcare facilities and clinics, AI-powered data-driven insights can empower the personalised treatment and medication approach more than ever before. Thanks to the large medical databases and other datasets that are going to be exposed to AI, gene analysis can allow the discovery of personalised medication.</p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>The Challenges and Key Consideration for Embracing AI in Healthcare </b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">In spite of the wide ranging benefits and awesome roles that AI is going to play for the healthcare industry as a whole, we must admit that the path to AI adoption is not going to be without challenges. There are regulatory aspects that can slow the pace of AI adoption and there is also the huge challenge of educating traditional healthcare professionals about the AI and its possibilities and promises.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><a href="https://www.fda.gov/home">FDA</a> has already come with a regulatory framework for approving such AI-based medical applications and software solutions. But still, in many parts of the fast-paced testing and approval of such software applications looks to be improbable. Educating medical professionals with the attributes of AI-based medical tools and intelligent software applications is another big challenge. The last but not the least of all challenges is maintaining data security and privacy of user information as AI-based apps are likely to handle a lot of patient data.</p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Conclusion</b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">One of the biggest beneficiaries of AI is going to be healthcare facilities and applications. Though healthcare AI is still at its very nascent state, in the years to come we can expect a rapid proliferation of this.</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/how-artificial-intelligence-is-transforming-healthcare-it-systems/">How Artificial Intelligence Is Transforming Healthcare IT Systems?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog">CMARIX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
									<featured_image>http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/artificial-intelligence-in-healthcare-software-development.png</featured_image>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Benefits, Pitfalls and Best Practices of Incorporating Robotic Process Automation (RPA) in Enterprise Software Projects</title>
		<link>http://192.168.1.163/blog/the-benefits-pitfalls-and-best-practices-of-incorporating-robotic-process-automation-rpa-in-enterprise-software-projects/</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 14:20:53 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Atman Rathod]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Website Development]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://192.168.1.163/blog/?p=12932</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Robotic process automation (RPA) is increasingly enjoying the favour of the enterprise leaders for streamlined software development, operational efficiency and cost advantages. Thanks to RPA the enterprise software projects can automate a multitude of common development tasks working based on rules. This creates more room for the developers to take care of more valuable tasks. &#8230; </p>
<p class="link-more"><a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/the-benefits-pitfalls-and-best-practices-of-incorporating-robotic-process-automation-rpa-in-enterprise-software-projects/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "The Benefits, Pitfalls and Best Practices of Incorporating Robotic Process Automation (RPA) in Enterprise Software Projects"</span></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/the-benefits-pitfalls-and-best-practices-of-incorporating-robotic-process-automation-rpa-in-enterprise-software-projects/">The Benefits, Pitfalls and Best Practices of Incorporating Robotic Process Automation (RPA) in Enterprise Software Projects</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog">CMARIX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify">Robotic process automation (RPA) is increasingly enjoying the favour of the enterprise leaders for streamlined software development, operational efficiency and cost advantages. Thanks to RPA the enterprise software projects can automate a multitude of common development tasks working based on rules. This creates more room for the developers to take care of more valuable tasks. Apart from these advantages many enterprises and <a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/software-product-development.html"><b>digital product development companies</b></a> also prefer RPA for the express purpose of automating processes by introducing advanced technologies such as artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning (ML).</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">So, in more than one way RPA has proved to be valuable for enterprise software projects. Here through this blog post we are going to explain the definition, benefits, some pitfalls and shortcomings and the best practices to introduce RPA in software projects.</p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>What Is Robotic Process Automation (RPA)?</b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12934 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Robotic-Process-Automation.png" alt="Robotic Process Automation " srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Robotic-Process-Automation.png 1600w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Robotic-Process-Automation-300x192.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Robotic-Process-Automation-768x492.png 768w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Robotic-Process-Automation-1024x656.png 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><a href="https://www.thedailystar.net/online/news/robotic-process-automation-can-be-game-changer-financial-sector-1957333">Robotic Process Automation</a> (RPA) is software application to automate multitude of tasks in enterprise environments. In the context of software development, RPA helps completing mundane, common and repetitive tasks. An RPA tool allows the enterprises to configure and interpret software applications for various tasks such as processing transactions, manipulating data, communicating with other applications  and triggering responses. RPA solutions make significant impact in enterprise environments ranging from facilitating automatic email responses through bots, automating tasks in ERP systems and many others.</p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Key Benefits of RPA</b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">RPA by automating tasks in enterprises enhances productivity and efficiency while reducing the staffing cost to a minimum. Thanks to the implementation of RPA, banks and financial organisations just by applying a few dozens bots can take on multitude of processes and serve millions of customer requests. Apart from allowing huge capacity enhancements with no significant cost this helps banks and financial organisations get things done with less employees.</p>

<ul>
 	<li><b>Easy and Non-Disruptive Implementation
</b></li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify">While these big business benefits are already well known about the bots, they can be integrated in a system without involving too much process complexity. Bots can easily be integrated in an enterprise system without causing any disruption in the present software systems that the organisations are using. On the other hand, by automating the mundane and low-key tasks the businesses can always make their processes better and more efficient.</p>

<ul>
 	<li><b>Intelligent Automation</b><b>
</b></li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12935 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Intelligent-Automation.png" alt="Intelligent Automation" srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Intelligent-Automation.png 1280w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Intelligent-Automation-300x169.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Intelligent-Automation-768x432.png 768w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Intelligent-Automation-1024x576.png 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">The RPA can further add value to the enterprises by combining the power of latest cognitive technologies such as natural language processing (NLP), speech recognition, machine learning, etc. While automation is already taking place across enterprises, intelligent automation is further widening the scope of automating tasks. Instead of only automating simple and repetitive tasks, intelligent automation with these technologies can help automating many complex and demanding tasks as well.</p>

<ul>
 	<li><b>Faster ROI Growth</b><b>
</b></li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12936 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/faster.png" alt="faster" srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/faster.png 800w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/faster-300x225.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/faster-768x576.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">The implementation of RPA can result in a significant boost of ROI growth for businesses. We already gave several examples of companies and service providers having benefited from RPA in terms of cost competitiveness, ROI and efficiency. For example, an HR firm that used to process thousands of sick leave applications and certificates consuming several weeks of time, can now complete the entire task in just around two days with zero errors. Undoubtedly, this huge impact directly converts to great return on investment.</p>

<ul>
 	<li><b>Better Customer Service</b><b>
</b></li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12937 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/batter-services.png" alt="" srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/batter-services.png 800w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/batter-services-300x225.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/batter-services-768x576.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">One of the biggest impacts of implementing RPA is the significant improvement in customer service. Apart from fast pacing the processes and reducing the human resources and cost, RPA implementation actually minimises the errors in customer query handling and processing different service requests. Precision, timeless and higher productivity are key benefits of RPA that make your customer service better.</p>

<ul>
 	<li><b>Some Shortcomings of RPA
</b></li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify">In spite of the awesome advantages that RPA is widely acclaimed for, it has its shortcomings and pitfalls as well. RPA in many industries can directly impact employment and push industries to reduce their manpower. RPA according to Forrester Research can contribute to a whopping 230 million job losses which amounts to around 9% of the worldwide working population.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">As of now, the implementation of hundreds of bots for automating tasks had a mixed reaction. While some industries could implement RPA easily, there are several industries that actually struggled to implement bots because of the complexities and the increasing cost. Moreover, some minor changes in the software implementation requirements can make weeks of work and efforts irrelevant.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/inquiry.html?utm_source=CTA_Blogimg"><img class="size-full wp-image-12938 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA.png" alt="CTA" srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA.png 951w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA-300x85.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA-768x219.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></a></p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Best Practices for RPA Implementation</b><b> </b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12939 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/RPA-Implementation.png" alt="RPA Implementation" srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/RPA-Implementation.png 512w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/RPA-Implementation-300x225.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 512px) 100vw, 512px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">In spite of all the benefits and shortcomings that we mentioned above, the value proposition of RPA neither can be written off nor can be fully agreed upon without understanding the practices that make such implementation successful. Yes, getting the value from RPA implementation largely depends upon how well you implement it in your business. Here we explain some effective tips and best practices.</p>
&nbsp;
<ul>
 	<li><b>Create Achievable Expectations:
</b></li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify">While implementing RPA COOs should go slow in setting expectations and should start with the minimum basic outcomes and gradually should set expectations higher as the system scales up.</p>

<ul>
 	<li><b>Keep Business Impact Into Consideration:</b></li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify">RPA is taken up by companies to achieve enhanced efficiency with reduced cost and thus to achieve better ROI. But if automation just reduces the level of customer satisfaction, this can be counterproductive. So, make sure replacing human communication with bots doesn&#8217;t compromise the quality of customer service.</p>

<ul>
 	<li><b>Make Sure Design and Change Management is Handled Efficiently</b>:</li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify">Many RPA implementations simply fail due to the poor bot architecture design and non-efficient management of changes that break the system flow. These two areas should be well planned in advance for professional handling.</p>
&nbsp;
<ul>
 	<li><b>Make Sure You Stick To The Original Objective</b>:</li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify">While automating data management tasks, many COOs by implementing ML programs actually lose the sight of their original objective and the scope of implementation. This often results in turning the bot project for data query solving to a fully fledged ML project.</p>

<ul>
 	<li><b>Not Planning For Obstacles</b>:</li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify">Failing to plan the obstacles and roadblocks in implementing the RPA is another common mistake that COOs and the enterprise management should keep in mind. You need to program the bots to take care of tasks that your company needs on a priority basis. While doing so, make sure you alerts regarding a system failure at any given point of time.</p>

<ul>
 	<li><b>Share The Excellence and Skills on RPA Implementation</b>:</li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify">The RPA implementation is still at its nascent stage and hence there is a lot of scope for improvement and value additions. To make this value addition happen, the industries should share their expertise, implementation best practices and expert advice.</p>

<ul>
 	<li><b>Go Slow In RPA Implementation</b>:</li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify">finally, all of us are heading towards a more bot ruled future but just because of that we cannot allow bots to take away all non-expert jobs and human roles in organisations. The best approach is to implement the RPA slowly so that many employees can enhance their skills and acquire new relevance in a bot-powered industrial setup.</p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Conclusion</b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Since enterprise software solutions require a pretty volume of rigorous tasks focused on quality and scalable output, the bots can be highly effective in getting things done quicker while creating more room for the developers to concentrate on more important things.</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/the-benefits-pitfalls-and-best-practices-of-incorporating-robotic-process-automation-rpa-in-enterprise-software-projects/">The Benefits, Pitfalls and Best Practices of Incorporating Robotic Process Automation (RPA) in Enterprise Software Projects</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog">CMARIX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
									<featured_image>http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Robotic-Process-Automation-RPA-in-enterprise-software-development.png</featured_image>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Authorise.net CIM Extension: Key Benefits and Ways to Integrate with Magento 2</title>
		<link>http://192.168.1.163/blog/authorise-net-cim-extension-key-benefits-and-ways-to-integrate-with-magento-2/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 13:51:43 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Atman Rathod]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Magento Development]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://192.168.1.163/blog/?p=12926</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>Authorize.Net is known to be the world&#8217;s leading payment gateway that caters to an overwhelming 400,000 merchants and is still counting. Like most sophisticated payment gateways they also help you to process customer payments from credit and debit cards straight to a website. Just by having an Authorize.Net account, you can avail of their extension &#8230; </p>
<p class="link-more"><a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/authorise-net-cim-extension-key-benefits-and-ways-to-integrate-with-magento-2/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Authorise.net CIM Extension: Key Benefits and Ways to Integrate with Magento 2"</span></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/authorise-net-cim-extension-key-benefits-and-ways-to-integrate-with-magento-2/">Authorise.net CIM Extension: Key Benefits and Ways to Integrate with Magento 2</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog">CMARIX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify"><span style="font-weight: 400">Authorize.Net is known to be the world&#8217;s leading payment gateway that caters to an overwhelming 400,000 merchants and is still counting. Like most sophisticated payment gateways they also help you to process customer payments from credit and debit cards straight to a website. Just by having an Authorize.Net account, you can avail of their extension for your website. Obviously, you need to pay an annual subscription fee that varies as per the payment processing value or number of transactions.  </span></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><span style="font-weight: 400">For any </span><a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/magento-ecommerce-development-services.html"><span style="font-weight: 400">Magento Development Company</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, this extension comes as the invariable first choice for integrating a payment gateway. No wonder, Authorize.Net&#8217;s Customer Information Manager (CIM) service makes payment processing for e-commerce websites much easier and ensures optimum convenience in terms of transactions. The company also offers an array of advanced features that other payment methods are barely capable of. </span></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><span style="font-weight: 400">Before we explain the steps of integrating this extension to the Magento store, let us have a quick look at the key features and benefits of the platform.</span></p>

<ul>
 	<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Authorize.Net CIM on the Magento2 module offers support for a multitude of standard payment options barely leaving any popular one. </span></li>
 	<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">It allows customers securely storing credit cards to ensure rapid checkout while fully maintaining PCI compliance.</span></li>
 	<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">The extension offers a very easy to use &#8216;Manage My Cards&#8217; interface to add, store, and replace cards into their account. </span></li>
 	<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">It allows using different Authorize.Net accounts for different websites and web stores. </span></li>
 	<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Supports ParadoxLabs Adaptive Subscriptions extension. </span></li>
 	<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">As for securing the data the communication with </span><a href="https://www.authorize.net/"><span style="font-weight: 400">Authorize.Net </span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">is covered with TLS encryption. Moreover, security-critical data is not saved on the server. A secure token-based system is used to allow checkout with stored card information. </span></li>
</ul>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>How to Integrate Authorize.Net with Magento 2? </b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12927 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Authorize-Net-Magento-2-1.jpg" alt="How to Integrate Authorize.Net with Magento 2? " srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Authorize-Net-Magento-2-1.jpg 768w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Authorize-Net-Magento-2-1-300x156.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><span style="font-weight: 400">Authorize.Net Direct Post comes as the most useful extension for payment gateway solutions for Magento web stores. It is particularly effective if your store has the presence of too many merchants who manage their checkout pages. It is also proved to be more essential for web stores having merchants who already have accounts on Authorize.Net. The extension will give them more ease of carrying out transactions without glitches. The best thing is while using this extension, customers can actually complete the entire transaction without really leaving the Magento e-commerce store. No wonder most</span><a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/ecommerce-web-development-services.html"><span style="font-weight: 400"> custom eCommerce solution services</span></a> <span style="font-weight: 400">prefer this extension for payment gateway. </span></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><span style="font-weight: 400">Now let us show you configuring this extension or adding this extension to Magento 2. It involves the following steps. </span></p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Step 1:</b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><span style="font-weight: 400">In this step, you need to prepare the look and feel of the Authorize.Net Direct Post payment method that would be displayed on the checkout page of the web store. Here are the exact instructions to follow. </span></p>

<ul>
 	<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Go to the Admin sidebar and click on the Stores &gt; Settings &gt; Configuration.</span></li>
 	<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Then just go to the left panel and select Sales &gt; Payment Methods.</span></li>
 	<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Now click again to open the Authorize.Net Direct Post section and here you can set the options.</span></li>
 	<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Right in the field that has been enabled, set “Yes” and the activate Authorize.Net Direct Post is activated.</span></li>
 	<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">In the field for Set Payment Action, choose “Authorize Only” for authorising the Authorize.Net to accept funds from customers besides creating order in stores. </span></li>
 	<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Now you need to create an invoice and mention the customer funds. </span></li>
 	<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">You can also choose the option “Authorize and Capture” to allow Authorize.Net to capture customer’s funds and create the order as well as an invoice. </span></li>
 	<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">In the field for Title, type a new name for Authorize.Net Direct Post for displaying on the checkout page or you can just leave it with the default one. </span></li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify"><b>Learn</b><span style="font-weight: 400">: </span><a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/the-role-of-magento-payment-gateways-in-magento-store-development/"><span style="font-weight: 400">The Role Of Magento Payment Gateways In Magento Store Development</span></a></p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Step 2:</b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><span style="font-weight: 400">Now you need to set the basement or complete the process of giving your Authorize.Net merchant account. Here are the exact instructions to follow.</span></p>

<ul>
 	<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Enter the credential and the value of your merchant account in the API Login ID, Transaction Key, and Merchant MD5 fields. enter your credentials and hash value from your Authorize.Net merchant account. To see the hash value go to the Authorize.Net website at Account &gt; Settings &gt; Security Settings &gt; MD5-Hash.</span></li>
 	<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Now right in the field for New Order Status, set Processed Ogone Payment or Processing as per the transaction type.</span></li>
 	<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Select ‘Yes’ for the Test Mode field to configure for the test environment. Just when the test results are positive turn the Test Mode negative by selecting “No”. </span></li>
 	<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Type the new URLs in the Gateway URL and URL fields for Transaction Details. In case of using a temporary URL that you received for testing, always restore the original one for actual transactions.</span></li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify"><a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/inquiry.html?utm_source=CTA_Blogimg"><img class="size-full wp-image-12930 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image998.png" alt="CTA inquiry" srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image998.png 951w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image998-300x85.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image998-768x219.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /> </a></p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Step 3:</b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><span style="font-weight: 400">This step is for guidance about the common configuration requirements for the entire process. Here are the exact instructions to follow. </span></p>

<ul>
 	<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Mention the acceptable or customer-friendly currencies in the Accepted Currency field.</span></li>
 	<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Set the Debug option to “Yes” to save all the activity logs taken place in between the store and the Authorize.Net.</span></li>
 	<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Set “Yes” for the Email Customer for sending the email communication to customers and mention your business email address in the field for Merchant’s Email.</span></li>
 	<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">In the box for Credit Card Types, choose all types of accepted credit cards for the store.</span></li>
 	<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Set “Yes” for Credit Card Verification to make sure customers enter a value for verifying the card.</span></li>
 	<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">In the field for Applicable Countries, select “All Allowed Countries” to authorise Authorize.Net Direct Post to accept payments from customers across all countries as mentioned in the store configuration or select “Specific Countries” to do the same from selected countries. </span></li>
 	<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">In the fields for Minimum Order Total and Maximum Order Total, mention the order value to qualify to make payment through this method.</span></li>
 	<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">In the field for Sort Order, give a number denoting the position of the payment method among other payment methods listed in the checkout page. </span></li>
</ul>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Conclusion</b><span style="font-weight: 400"> </span></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><span style="font-weight: 400">While Magento leads the e-commerce space as the most versatile and customisable platform, this leading payment gateway extension just helps Magento deliver a more customer-friendly shopping experience. Two are just ideally made for each other to deliver a great checkout experience.</span></p>
&nbsp;<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/authorise-net-cim-extension-key-benefits-and-ways-to-integrate-with-magento-2/">Authorise.net CIM Extension: Key Benefits and Ways to Integrate with Magento 2</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog">CMARIX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
									<featured_image>http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Authorise.net-CIM-Extension.png</featured_image>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Key Security Practices That Most Leading eCommerce Audit Specialists Prescribe</title>
		<link>http://192.168.1.163/blog/key-security-practices-that-most-leading-ecommerce-audit-specialists-prescribe/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 14:18:28 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Atman Rathod]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[eCommerce]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://192.168.1.163/blog/?p=12914</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>E-commerce stores experience the most scorching heat of competition among all web based businesses just because it is often the user experience that drives user engagement and business conversion. User experience and store performance together works like a double edged sword for any e-commerce store. On the one hand, it offers a level playing field &#8230; </p>
<p class="link-more"><a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/key-security-practices-that-most-leading-ecommerce-audit-specialists-prescribe/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Key Security Practices That Most Leading eCommerce Audit Specialists Prescribe"</span></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/key-security-practices-that-most-leading-ecommerce-audit-specialists-prescribe/">Key Security Practices That Most Leading eCommerce Audit Specialists Prescribe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog">CMARIX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify">E-commerce stores experience the most scorching heat of competition among all web based businesses just because it is often the user experience that drives user engagement and business conversion. User experience and store performance together works like a double edged sword for any e-commerce store. On the one hand, it offers a level playing field for a small business to compete with a big brand just by offering a high performance web shopping experience and on the other hand, a store in spite of great brand value and product range just can be sidelined because of poor user experience.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">No wonder, every e-commerce store gives user experience so much importance more than anything else. Well, this is why <a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/product-auditing.html"><b>product auditing</b></a> for the e-commerce store is so important. Auditing just leaves bare the performance issues, loading problems, user experience skirmishes, security vulnerabilities and user pain points that are continuously pulling down user engagement and sales.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">But above all, the most merciless aspect is the e-commerce security that no store can compromise for just a few transactions. Just once with one customer you make an impression that his transaction data is compromised and the information spreads like bonfire drastically bringing your brand reputation. So security audit is the most important aspect that your store should give maximum priority.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Here we are going to explain the key security areas that most e-commerce audits primarily focus upon.</p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Evaluating User Authentication</b><b> </b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12918 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/User-Authentication.png" alt="User Authentication " srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/User-Authentication.png 800w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/User-Authentication-300x225.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/User-Authentication-768x576.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">The first and foremost objective of the e-commerce security audit should focus upon the user authentication measures that the store uses. Does it use two factor authentication and strong passwords? How hygienic the password policy is to prevent malicious intrusions? Does the store allow social login to help users save time? Does it offer other advanced authentication technologies such as biometric authentication or face recognition? The security audit should ask all these questions.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">As for passwords, make sure your audit recommends using complex passwords comprising upper and lower cases, numbers and special characters. To protect your credentials the store can also ask you to change the password every six months just like any netbanking app. It is also important to ask users not to use the same password twice within a year. On top of all these, your store must ensure using two factor authentication to keep security risks at bay.</p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Auditing The Website Code</b><b> </b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12919 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/website.png" alt="website" srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/website.png 800w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/website-300x225.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/website-768x576.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">The e-commerce audit should also take into consideration all the security risks emanating from the coding errors and faulty code lines that can easily be fixed. If you have built your e-commerce store from the ground up and customised too many things, there are better chances that the underlying code may have some fault lines or problems.</p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Using HTTPS and SSL</b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12920 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/HTTPS-and-SSL.png" alt="HTTPS and SSL" srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/HTTPS-and-SSL.png 800w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/HTTPS-and-SSL-300x225.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/HTTPS-and-SSL-768x576.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">HyperText Transfer Protocol Secure (HTTPS) is the more secure protocol for the internet domains that prevent malicious attempts to force their way in any website. Since HTTP becomes HTTPS protocol with the addition of SSL security certificate that certifies the domain as secure, security audit always finds HTTP with security shortcomings. Because of having security certificates, HTTPS websites are more trusted by the web users.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">The best thing is businesses for the purpose of enabling the HTTPS, need to get a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) certificate. After getting this certificate, your website will be deemed to be fit and secure for receiving and sending data over the internet. Apart from establishing a security standard for the web store, HTTPS protocol also enjoys priority in Google search rank over HTTP websites as the former is trusted more by Google. The most important thing is, many tech savvy and seasoned online shoppers will simply find a web store secure and trustworthy because of the SSL certificate that turns a HTTP website into HTTPS website.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/inquiry.html?utm_source=CTA_Blogimg"><img class="size-full wp-image-12921 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image-20.png" alt="CTA" srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image-20.png 951w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image-20-300x85.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image-20-768x219.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></a></p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Auditing The eCommerce Platform Security</b><b> </b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12922 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/eCommerce-Platform-Security.png" alt=" eCommerce Platform Security" srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/eCommerce-Platform-Security.png 800w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/eCommerce-Platform-Security-300x225.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/eCommerce-Platform-Security-768x576.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Now, e-commerce audits should take care of the security issues and vulnerabilities with the e-commerce platforms. There are multitudes of e-commerce platforms out there with a variety of features, design attributes and features. Similarly, these e-commerce platforms also vary in terms of security elements and security features. The e-commerce audit should evaluate whether the platform offers SSL certificates, inbuilt encrypted payment gateway, secure authentication systems, automatic backups, security scans, checkups and alerts.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">The managed e-commerce platforms that pretty much take care of everything starting from the store set up to the hosting to security and customisation, are better in terms of security features. But managed platforms offer the best security and other features with their top plans and hence are more expensive.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">If you go for a self hosted eCommerce store platform, you can still build a rock solid security by following the best security practices and using the right plugins and tools for e-commerce security. When going for an e-commerce platform where you have better control on each and every aspect of design and development you can actually strengthen security gradually as the traffic increases.</p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Auditing The Data Sensitivity</b><b> </b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12923 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Auditing-The-Data-Sensitivity.png" alt="Auditing The Data Sensitivity " srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Auditing-The-Data-Sensitivity.png 800w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Auditing-The-Data-Sensitivity-300x225.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Auditing-The-Data-Sensitivity-768x576.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">How your webstore deals with the most valuable and mission critical data and what kind of measures you have to keep this data out of the reach of hackers and intruders is a crucial aspect of e-commerce store audit. How good is an e-commerce store in safeguarding the privacy and security of the user data and transactions? This is the most important question that your e-commerce audit should find out.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">The key consideration is whether the data collected from the customer to carry out transactions are used only once or are stored. In the second case, the stored user data becomes more vulnerable to security glitches. On the other hand, the more data a store collects from its customers, the more vulnerable the situation gets from the security point of view. This is why, it is advisable to collect only the most essential user data and once it is used make sure the data is destroyed or dumped into oblivion. In case saving some information about the users is absolutely necessary, make sure the data remains encrypted to prevent unsolicited access.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><b>Learn More: </b><a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/why-code-audits-are-essential-and-what-purpose-does-it-serve/">Why Code Audits are Essential and What Purpose Does It Serve?</a></p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Auditing The Plugins and Themes</b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Now let us point out the biggest source of security vulnerabilities and security risks across multitude of e-commerce stores all over the globe. Every e-commerce platform comes with a multitude of themes for shaping the look and feel of web stores. Not all themes come from certified publishers and irrespective of the publishers themes can have bugs and issues leading to security risks.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Plugins can often add to the security risks as they are built by unknown publishers and come with a lot of security issues. Moreover, often many plugins just remain without updates for years and they become the source of security risks. An e-commerce audit must find update history, credentials and security issues of the themes and plugins.</p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Conclusion</b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Security audit does the job of guarding your online store from unwanted and malicious data breaches and security attacks that can put your store off its balance. After conducting the thorough security audit, automatically you know the specific areas where you need to improve for delivering a better shopping experience.</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/key-security-practices-that-most-leading-ecommerce-audit-specialists-prescribe/">Key Security Practices That Most Leading eCommerce Audit Specialists Prescribe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog">CMARIX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
									<featured_image>http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Ensure-security-audit-of-your-eCommerce-store.png</featured_image>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Smart Way For Automotive Industry To Modernize With Android App Development</title>
		<link>http://192.168.1.163/blog/the-smart-way-for-automotive-industry-to-modernize-with-android-app-development/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 14:28:28 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Atman Rathod]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Mobile App Development]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://192.168.1.163/blog/?p=12906</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p>The connected in-car infotainment system from Android platform is there shaping the vision of Google delivering a seamless and smart experience for the Android users while driving and boarding their vehicles. Smart and connected car infotainment systems have already become a reality for the past several years and we have several third-party mobile apps allowing &#8230; </p>
<p class="link-more"><a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/the-smart-way-for-automotive-industry-to-modernize-with-android-app-development/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "The Smart Way For Automotive Industry To Modernize With Android App Development"</span></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/the-smart-way-for-automotive-industry-to-modernize-with-android-app-development/">The Smart Way For Automotive Industry To Modernize With Android App Development</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog">CMARIX</a>.</p>
]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify">The connected in-car infotainment system from Android platform is there shaping the vision of Google delivering a seamless and smart experience for the Android users while driving and boarding their vehicles. Smart and connected car infotainment systems have already become a reality for the past several years and we have several third-party mobile apps allowing us to stay connected between the in-car display and the smartphones. But the Android automotive OS brought together car infotainment and smartphone apps within one single ecosystem and OS platform.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Android Automotive OS sharing the similar look, feel and user experience of Google Android platform is tailor-suited for present day cars. As the demand for connected car infotainment systems are increasing rapidly creating exceptional demands for apps for the Android Automotive OS, it is high time to explain the potential of the platform and development of automotive apps for this platform. It is expected that the new platform will also help <a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/logistic-and-transportation-product-development.html"><b>logistics and transportation software development services</b></a> to build android automotive apps for the truckers and logistics vehicle drivers.</p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>What is Android Automotive OS?</b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12908 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/ezgif.com-video-to-gif-9.gif" alt="" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><a href="https://source.android.com/devices/automotive/start/what_automotive"><b>Android Automotive OS</b></a> is an Android operating system version tailored to create and run apps on the Android-based car infotainment systems. The vehicle owners integrate the Android based infotainment device in their cars that allows running Android apps and staying connected to the Android smartphones of the owners.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Earlier you needed to use the smartphone to stay connected with a car infotainment system. Now, the Android infotainment device attached to the car can run all Android apps for media playing, GPS positioning, web browsing and all in-car information and entertainment services. This will of course broaden the market opportunities for any <a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/android-application-development-services.html"><b>Android app development company</b></a> with a new Android platform besides mobile and wearables.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Let us explain some of the biggest advantages of Android Automotive OS that car owners and users will find really great.</p>

<ul>
 	<li><b>Voice Control for Distraction Free Driving
</b></li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify">Distractions during driving remains to be one of the biggest safety concerns for drivers and passengers all over the world. Using smartphones for conversation, messaging and browsing apps regularly cause thousands of road accidents taking millions of lives. This is where Android Automotive can play a powerful role by reducing such distractions through voice control.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">With Android Automotive OS running your car, you can just take control of many actions just by using voice commands. From making quick phone calls to turning on music to changing the music track to sending a quick message to just opening the GPS map for traffic guidance, you can do it all with simple voice commands while your attention remains fixed on the road.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/inquiry.html?utm_source=CTA_Blogimg"><img class="size-full wp-image-12909 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image2535.png" alt="CTA" srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image2535.png 951w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image2535-300x85.png 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/CTA_Image2535-768x219.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></a></p>

<ul>
 	<li><b>A Connected Android Experience
</b></li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12910 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/A-Connected-Android-Experience.jpg" alt="A Connected Android Experience" srcset="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/A-Connected-Android-Experience.jpg 800w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/A-Connected-Android-Experience-300x210.jpg 300w, http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/A-Connected-Android-Experience-768x538.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 767px) 89vw, (max-width: 1000px) 54vw, (max-width: 1071px) 543px, 580px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Android as the operating system for running the vast majority of smartphones in the market is sought after for a connected experience across connected devices. The new Android Automotive OS is only helping this ecosystem to gain further stronghold while most car owners will gain a connected experience. The same Android apps running on the in-car infotainment system and the smartphones will allow more ease of use and seamless user experience in different contexts.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Apart from benefiting the car owners with a seamless experience, the same can be highly beneficial for boosting app marketing and revenue flow. Thanks to this, there can be a new breed of apps targeting different car models and preferences of drivers and car owners.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify"><b>Learn </b>: <a href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/features-and-facts-of-successful-travel-app-that-attract-customers/">Features And Facts Of Successful Travel App That Attract Customers</a></p>

<ul>
 	<li><b>Intelligent Communication and Driving in the Offing
</b></li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify">We already have discovered self driving cars that just didn&#8217;t hit the road because of several security concerns. While driverless cars are still going through rigorous evaluations concerning on-road safety, their role in making lives easier with easy transport solutions cannot be debated. The emergence of Android Automotive OS is a significant step towards this connected reality powered by driverless cars and the connected in-car entertainment systems.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">While driverless vehicles are still exposed to all sorts of on-road risks, the intelligent in-car systems do the impressive job of detecting driver behaviour and habits that can pose threats and chances of accidents. The Android Automotive OS in this regard will offer the greatest advantages in terms of automating various processes and making driver interactions with the digital apps easier while driving a vehicle.</p>

<ul>
 	<li><b>Lets Begin with the Media Apps</b></li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12912 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/ezgif.com-video-to-gif-10.gif" alt="" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Just as Android Automotive started its journey and the first car with this impressive system has hit the road, most developers agree that media apps catering music, radio stations and podcasts are the most popular ones for the platform now. Media apps are likely to be the most popular showcasing the benefits of the platform primarily to the users.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">But wait, there are several complications they need to ditch in the process. The maze of original equipment manufacturers (OEM) in the industry, the diverse screen sizes, input methods and user preferences all will boast of a whole range of options and equal length of complications. This will take some time to stabilise before the market is flooded by the Android apps for this new in-car ecosystem.</p>

<ul>
 	<li><b>App Bundles and Diverse APKs</b></li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify">It is quite likely that the developers will continue to build apps for diverse platforms and not only for Android Automotive. Naturally, there will be a lot of technical considerations including the shared code or reusability of the codebase across platforms and the APKs that can be used for building multiple versions of the same app.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">Most developers agree that reusing most of the code gives them the added advantage of building an app easily and in less time. The time tested approach to have a single project at the top along with several modules is most effective and efficient. This approach also allows creating a single Android App Bundle (.aab) comprising multiple device specific versions including the one meant for the Android Automotive platform.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify">This approach is also effective because the users can get their required app version or the portion of the app bundle right from the Play Store through Dynamic Delivery of modules. This approach will also allow stripping off both the assets and the modules so that the users can only download and access the parts they need for configuring their devices. This will further help them to save device storage and bandwidth by staying clear off the unnecessary parts.</p>

<ul>
 	<li><b>Google Play for Android Automotive
</b></li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify"><img class="size-full wp-image-12911 aligncenter" src="http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/android-auto-search.gif" alt="android-auto-search" /></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">One of the greatest advantages for this automotive platform is that it will come with the power of the Google Play store and its services. Both the Google Play services and the SDKs from Google will be available to the mobile app projects and the app projects for Android Automotive. Of course, there are several differences between the mobile app and the automotive platform, particularly the UI/UX aspects of the automotive apps. The app SDKs and Play services will be optimised for the UI/UX elements of the car interface.</p>

<ul>
 	<li><b>A Few Words About the User Experience
</b></li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: justify">One of the most crucial aspects of Android Automotive is the rich user experience. Particularly in respect of playing media while driving we can expect several new UX elements. But these new UX elements will not end with the media apps, they will also play an important role in respect of crucial functions such as messaging and calls. In terms of user experience Android Automotive will offer several crucial elements drivers feel useful and crucial while sitting behind the wheel.</p>
<p style="color: #21759b;font-size: 18pt;font-family: sf_ui_displaysemibold"><b>Conclusion</b></p>
<p style="text-align: justify">In all regards it seems that Android Automotive OS is going to be a resounding success by taking the Android platform benefits to the modern and digitally equipped vehicles. Just as in the case of mobile apps, Android Automotive is going to be the leading OS app platform for the in-vehicle infotainment systems.</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog/the-smart-way-for-automotive-industry-to-modernize-with-android-app-development/">The Smart Way For Automotive Industry To Modernize With Android App Development</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://192.168.1.163/blog">CMARIX</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
									<featured_image>http://192.168.1.163/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Why-to-develop-mobile-apps-for-Android-Automotive-OS.png</featured_image>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>